[
  {
    "question": "question 1",
    "answer1": "answer1",
    "answer2": "answer2",
    "answer3": "answer3",
    "answer4": "answer4",
    "correct": "2",
    "fact": "The severed head of a sea slug can grow a whole new body."
  },
  {
    "question": "question 2",
    "answer1": "answer1",
    "answer2": "answer2",
    "answer3": "answer3",
    "answer4": "answer4",
    "correct": "3",
    "fact": "The world's smallest reptile was first reported in 2021."
  },
  {
    "question": "question 3",
    "answer1": "answer1",
    "answer2": "answer2",
    "answer3": "answer3",
    "answer4": "answer4",
    "correct": "1",
    "fact": "The feeling of getting lost inside a mall is known as the Gruen transfer."
  },
  {
    "question": "question 4",
    "answer1": "answer1",
    "answer2": "answer2",
    "answer3": "answer3",
    "answer4": "answer4",
    "correct": "4",
    "fact": "Humans are the only animals that blush."
  },
  {
    "question": "question 5",
    "answer1": "answer1",
    "answer2": "answer2",
    "answer3": "answer3",
    "answer4": "answer4",
    "correct": "2",
    "fact": "There's no such thing as pear cider."
  },
  {
    "question": "question 6",
    "answer1": "answer1",
    "answer2": "answer2",
    "answer3": "answer3",
    "answer4": "answer4",
    "correct": "2",
    "fact": "Goosebumps are meant to ward off predators."
  },
  {
    "question": "question 7",
    "answer1": "answer1",
    "answer2": "answer2",
    "answer3": "answer3",
    "answer4": "answer4",
    "correct": "3",
    "fact": "The moon has moonquakes."
  },
  {
    "question": "question 8",
    "answer1": "answer1",
    "answer2": "answer2",
    "answer3": "answer3",
    "answer4": "answer4",
    "correct": "1",
    "fact": "The heads on Easter Island have bodies."
  },
  {
    "question": "question 9",
    "answer1": "answer1",
    "answer2": "answer2",
    "answer3": "answer3",
    "answer4": "answer4",
    "correct": "4",
    "fact": "Some sea snakes can breathe through their skin."
  },
  {
    "question": "question 10",
    "answer1": "answer1",
    "answer2": "answer2",
    "answer3": "answer3",
    "answer4": "answer4",
    "correct": "3",
    "fact": "Many feet bones don't harden until you're an adult."
  }
]
